{"test_questions": [[{"question": "The difference between a PLA and a PAL is:", "opta": "The PLA has a programmable OR plane and a programmable AND plane, while the PAL only has a programmable AND plane.", "optb": "The PAL has a programmable OR plane and a programmable AND plane, while the PLA only has a programmable AND plane.", "optc": "The PAL has more possible product terms than the PLA.", "optd": "PALs and PLAs are the same thing.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ALM is the acronym for ________.", "opta": "Array Logic Matrix", "optb": "Arithmetic Logic Module", "optc": "Asynchronous Local Modulator", "optd": "Adaptive Logic Module", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The GAL16V8 has:", "opta": "16 dedicated inputs.", "optb": "8 special function pins.", "optc": "8 pins that are used as inputs or outputs.", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PALs tend to execute ________ logic.", "opta": "SAP", "optb": "SOP", "optc": "PLA", "optd": "SPD", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many pins are in an EDF10K70 package?", "opta": "70", "optb": "140", "optc": "240", "optd": "532", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A GAL is essentially a ________.", "opta": "non-reprogrammable PAL", "optb": "PAL that is programmed only by the manufacturer", "optc": "very large PAL", "optd": "reprogrammable PAL", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is an OTP device?", "opta": "Optical transporting port", "optb": "Octal transmitting pixel", "optc": "Operational topical portable", "optd": "One-time programmable", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many product terms can a MAX+Plus II compiler borrow from adjacent macrocells in the same LAB?", "opta": "0", "optb": "5", "optc": "10", "optd": "20", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Each programmable array logic (PAL) gate product is applied to an OR gate and, if combinational logic is desired, the product is ORed and then:", "opta": "the polarity fuse is restored", "optb": "sent to an inverter for output", "optc": "sent immediately to an output pin", "optd": "passed to the AND function for output", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "________ are used at the inputs of PAL/GAL devices in order to prevent input loading from a large number of AND gates.", "opta": "Simplified AND gates", "optb": "Fuses", "optc": "Buffers", "optd": "Latches", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A(n) ________ consists of a programmable array of AND gates that connects to a fixed array of OR gates and is usually OTP.", "opta": "GAL", "optb": "CPLD", "optc": "PAL", "optd": "SPLD", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is another name for digital circuitry called sequential logic?", "opta": "logic macrocell", "optb": "logic array", "optc": "flip-flop memory circuitry", "optd": "inverter", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When did the first PLD appear?", "opta": "More than 10 years ago", "optb": "More than 20 years ago", "optc": "More than 30 years ago", "optd": "More than 40 years ago", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SPLDs, CPLDs, and FPGAs are all which type of device?", "opta": "PAL", "optb": "PLD", "optc": "EPROM", "optd": "SRAM", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Cascade chains are closely associated with ________.", "opta": "CLBs", "optb": "SOP functions", "optc": "logic expansion", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FPLA is:", "opta": "a nonmemory programmable device.", "optb": "a programmable AND array.", "optc": "a programmable OR array.", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A(n) ________ is a section of embedded logic that is commonly found in FPGAs.", "opta": "LUT", "optb": "core", "optc": "DSP", "optd": "PI", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a FLEX10K, what two outputs will the LE produce?", "opta": "The LAB and the fast track", "optb": "ON and OFF", "optc": "Hi-Z and ON", "optd": "Hi-Z and OFF", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the major downfall of microprocessor/DSP systems?", "opta": "Speed\u2014they are too fast", "optb": "Speed\u2014they are too slow", "optc": "Too much flexibility", "optd": "Not enough flexibility", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ASIC stands for:", "opta": "advanced speed integrated circuit.", "optb": "advanced standard integrated circuit.", "optc": "application specific integrated circuit.", "optd": "application speedy integrated circuit.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A look-up table is simply a truth table with all the possible output connections listed with their desired input response.", "opta": "True", "optb": "False", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The final step in the device programming sequence is ________.", "opta": "compiling", "optb": "downloading", "optc": "simulation", "optd": "synthesis", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Most look-up tables in field-programmable gate arrays (FGPAs) use ________ inputs, resulting in ________ possible outputs.", "opta": "4,16", "optb": "8,16", "optc": "4,12", "optd": "6,12", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the defining difference between microprocessor/DSP systems and other digital systems?", "opta": "The digital system follows a programmed sequence of instructions that the designer specified.", "optb": "The microprocessor follows a programmed sequence of instructions that the designer specified.", "optc": "The digital system is faster.", "optd": "The microprocessor/DSP is faster.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Why have PLDs taken over so much of the market?", "opta": "One PLD does the work of many ICs.", "optb": "The PLDs are cheaper.", "optc": "Less power is required.", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CLB is the acronym for ________.", "opta": "Configurable Logic Block", "optb": "Configurable Logic Buffer", "optc": "Critical Logic Buffer", "optd": "Constant Logic Buffer", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What can the GAL22V10 do that the GAL16V8 cannot?", "opta": "It has an extra-large array.", "optb": "It is in-system programmable.", "optc": "It has twice the special function pins.", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The output of this circuit is always ________.", "opta": "1", "optb": "0", "optc": "A", "optd": "A", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A circuit that implements a combinational logic function by storing a list of output values that correspond to all possible input combinations is a(n) ________.", "opta": "output logic macrocell", "optb": "look-up table", "optc": "parallel logic expander", "optd": "logic element", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "By adding an OR gate to a simple programmable logic device (SPLD) the foundation for a(n) ________ is made possible.", "opta": "PAL", "optb": "PLA", "optc": "CPLD", "optd": "EEPROM", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What does the Altera FLEX10K PLD use in place of AND and OR arrays?", "opta": "Nothing, it uses AND and OR arrays.", "optb": "Look-up tables", "optc": "SRAM-based memory", "optd": "HPLD architecture", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PIA is an acronym for ________.", "opta": "Programmable Interface Array", "optb": "Post Integrated Array", "optc": "Programmable Input Array", "optd": "Programmable Interconnect Array", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which one of the following is an embedded function of the Stratix II FPGA?", "opta": "AND-OR logic", "optb": "Programmable SOP", "optc": "Digital signal processing", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In an OLMC, where does the FMUX signal go?", "opta": "OMUX", "optb": "D flip-flop", "optc": "Matrix", "optd": "PAL", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following testing procedures has one or more external moving parts?", "opta": "Bed-of-nails", "optb": "Flying probe", "optc": "EXTEST", "optd": "Boundary scan", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Field-programmable gate arrays (FGPAs) use ________ memory technology, which is ________.", "opta": "DRAM, nonvolatile", "optb": "SRAM, nonvolatile", "optc": "SRAM, volatile", "optd": "RAM, volatile", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A PAL16L8 has:", "opta": "10 inputs and 8 outputs.", "optb": "8 inputs and 8 outputs.", "optc": "16 inputs and 16 outputs.", "optd": "16 inputs and 8 outputs.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Now many times can a GAL be erased and reprogrammed?", "opta": "0", "optb": "At least 100", "optc": "At least 1000", "optd": "Over 10,000", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MPGA stands for:", "opta": "mass produced gated array.", "optb": "Morgan-Phillips gated array.", "optc": "memory programmed ROM.", "optd": "mask programmed ROM.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following increases the number of product terms by borrowing unused product from other macrocells?", "opta": "Shared expander", "optb": "Parallel expander", "optc": "Series expander", "optd": "Slice expander", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is a mode of operation of the GAL16V8?", "opta": "Simple mode", "optb": "Complex mode", "optc": "Registered mode", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following testing procedures uses the JTAG IEEE standard?", "opta": "Bed-of-nails", "optb": "Flying probe", "optc": "EXTEST", "optd": "Boundary scan", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The macrocells in a PAL/GAL are located ________.", "opta": "after the programmable AND arrays", "optb": "ahead of the programmable AND arrays", "optc": "at the input terminals", "optd": "at the output terminals", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The content of a simple programmable logic device (PLD) consists of:", "opta": "fuse-link arrays", "optb": "thousands of basic logic gates", "optc": "advanced sequential logic functions", "optd": "thousands of basic logic gates and advanced sequential logic functions", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is a major digital system category?", "opta": "Standard logic devices", "optb": "ASICs", "optc": "Microprocessor/DSP devices", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the input/output pin configuration of the GAL22V10?", "opta": "10 output pins and 12 input pins", "optb": "2 special-purpose pins", "optc": "8 pins that are either inputs or outputs", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The output of this circuit is always ________.", "opta": "1", "optb": "0", "optc": "A", "optd": "A", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What does a dot mean when placed on a PLD circuit diagram?", "opta": "A point that is programmable", "optb": "A point that cannot change", "optc": "An intersection of logic blocks", "optd": "An input or output point", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FPGA is the acronym for ________.", "opta": "Flexible Programming [of] Generic Assemblies", "optb": "Field Programmable Generic Array", "optc": "Field Programmable Gate Array", "optd": "Field Programmer's Gate Assembly", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many combinations are handled in an LUT?", "opta": "4", "optb": "8", "optc": "16", "optd": "32", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true?", "opta": "Altera uses PAL architecture and Xilinx uses PLA architecture.", "optb": "Altera uses PLA architecture and Xilinx uses PAL architecture.", "optc": "Altera and Xilinx both use PAL architecture.", "optd": "Altera and Xilinx both use PLA architecture.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the status of a tristate output buffer on a MAX7000S family device?", "opta": "It is permanently enabled or disabled.", "optb": "It is controlled by one of the two global output enable pins.", "optc": "It is controlled by other inputs or functions generated by other macrocells.", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GAL is an acronym for ________.", "opta": "Generic Array Logic", "optb": "General Array Logic", "optc": "Giant Array Logic", "optd": "Generic Analysis Logic", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What gives a GAL its flexibility?", "opta": "Its speed", "optb": "Its reprogrammable EPROM", "optc": "Its large logic arrays", "optd": "Its programmable OLMCs", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What programmable technology is used in FPGA devices?", "opta": "SRAM", "optb": "FLASH", "optc": "Antifuse", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is an EPM7128S?", "opta": "An Altera MAX7000S CPLD", "optb": "An Altera UP2", "optc": "A DeVry eSOC", "optd": "A BSR PL DT-2", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An SPLD listed as 22V10 has ________.", "opta": "10 inputs, 10 outputs, and requires a 22 V power source", "optb": "11 inputs, 11 outputs, and requires a 10 V power source", "optc": "22 inputs and 10 outputs", "optd": "10 inputs and 22 outputs", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The Altera MAX 7000 series ________.", "opta": "uses an E2PROM process technology", "optb": "can have between 2 and 16 LABS and I/O control blocks", "optc": "is available with DC supply voltages between 2.5 V and 5 V", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A macrocell basically contains ________.", "opta": "a programmable AND-OR gate array and some input buffers", "optb": "an OR-gate array and some output logic", "optc": "an AND-OR gate array and some output logic", "optd": "licensed programming", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The complex programmable logic device (CPLD) features a(n) ________ type of memory.", "opta": "volatile", "optb": "nonvolatile", "optc": "EPROM", "optd": "volitile EPROM", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many macrocells are in a MAX700S LAB?", "opta": "8", "optb": "16", "optc": "32", "optd": "64", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is not a type of PLD?", "opta": "SPLD", "optb": "HPLD", "optc": "CPLD", "optd": "FPGA", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An SPLD listed as 16H8 would have ________.", "opta": "active-HIGH outputs", "optb": "active-LOW outputs", "optc": "variable-level outputs", "optd": "latches at the outputs", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which type of PLD could be used to program basic logic functions?", "opta": "PLA", "optb": "PAL", "optc": "CPLD", "optd": "all the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The complex programmable logic device (CPLD) contains several PAL-type simple programmable logic devices (SPLDs) called:", "opta": "macrocells", "optb": "microcells", "optc": "AND/OR arrays", "optd": "fuse-link arrays", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which is not a part of a GAL16V8's OLMC?", "opta": "TSMUX", "optb": "OMUX", "optc": "FMUX", "optd": "PSMUX", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is PROM?", "opta": "SPLD", "optb": "QPLD", "optc": "HPLD", "optd": "PLD", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A slice consists of ________.", "opta": "only two logic cells", "optb": "between 2 and 8 logic cells", "optc": "up to 16 logic cells", "optd": "a single CLB", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Product terms are the outputs of which type of gate within a PLD array?", "opta": "OR", "optb": "XOR", "optc": "AND", "optd": "flip-flop", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}